<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <name>KSysGuard</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KSysGuard</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KSysGuard</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KSysGuard</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKSysGuardxx</name>
  <summary>Monitor running processes and system performance</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Controlador de processos en execució i rendiment del sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Actieve processen en systeemprestaties monitoren</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Стеження за процесами та швидкодією системи</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxMonitor running processes and system performancexx</summary>
  <icon type="stock">utilities-system-monitor</icon>
  <id>org.kde.ksysguard</id>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.ksysguard.desktop</launchable>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <description>
    <p>System Guard allows you to monitor information and statistics about your system.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El System Guard permet controlar la informació i les estadístiues del sistema.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">System Guard stelt u in staat informatie en statistieken over uw systeem te monitoren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Засіб стеження за системою надає вам змогу стежити за відомостями та статистичними даними щодо вашої системи.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxSystem Guard allows you to monitor information and statistics about your system.xx</p>
    <p>In addition to monitoring the local system, it can connect to remote systems running the System Guard Daemon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Addicionalment al monitoratge del sistema local, pot connectar-se a sistemes remots executant el dimoni del System Guard.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Naast het monitoren van het lokale systeem, kan het verbinden met systemen op afstand die de System Guard-daemon hebben geactiveerd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Окрім стеження за локальною системою, програма здатна з'єднуватися із віддаленими системами, де запущено фонову службу стеження за системою.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxIn addition to monitoring the local system, it can connect to remote systems running the System Guard Daemon.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=ksysguard</url>
  <url type="help">https://userbase.kde.org/KSysGuard</url>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org/applications/system/ksysguard</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/donate.php?app=org.kde.ksysguard</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://www.kde.org/images/screenshots/ksysguard.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
</component>
